Hello friends, welcome all. Today, the video I have brought for you will
talk about
core concepts. We will talk about hidden
stocks. When they are ready to flee, we will
try to learn how the situation is seen. We will talk
about opportunity risk through different stocks. We will
learn a lot while focusing on momentum and learning.
Before moving ahead, let me tell you that if
you have not yet subscribed to the channel, then
subscribe quickly. Press the bell icon so
that you will keep getting notifications. To
learn price action, you
can join by clicking on the membership join button. The
series of the price section
is very important. Learning, as I
told you, whenever you have time on the weekend,
do it. Practice. Practice is very
important. If you
start practicing, you will automatically start understanding things. If
not for six months, then for a year. If not for a year, then for a year and a half, if
not for a year and a half, then for two years. Things will keep
settling in your mind when you
practice on a regular basis. Two Point
System. We often mention the two
point system for double.  We've mentioned formations and
divergences many times,
using the MCD to understand divergence. So,
today, the first
learning that comes to us is that ICICI
Lombard General Insurance will show you
how. Look, its market capitalization has increased to
over 1 lakh crore. The debt on the company is
negligible, but the stock has
taught us a lot. Just look, you'll enjoy it. The
weekly chart
is very important for us, but if we ever get
to see such a situation on the weekly chart, it will be fun.
Look, on the weekly chart, we saw a 2-
point system here, and it
seemed like this stock is showing some momentum.
Look, point number one, point number
two, if you look carefully, you'll see this
lower low, but here the
MCD showed us divergence. As soon as we
show divergence, we see
positivity. This stock is
showing momentum now, but a little
consolidation happened here. So, this stock
showed us in October-November last year that
this stock was capable of running.
Now it can give a great rally anytime,
how did that thought process go, how did that
thought process go,
that thought process goes according to the larger time frame,
things crossed according to this two point system
and it looked like this in this consolidation zone, brother, this will
cross and can give a great ready here,
a big stock which is a
stock with big market cap, if you
look at it then you will say what are you talking about,
what a great situation this is, this ICICI
Lord General Insurance came in front of you on November 15
when its price was 1393 on
November 15, 1393, let me go to November 15, so
see, its pricing was around 1390,
after that neither it hit immediate stop loss
nor deep stop loss and
gave you a very good quality rally
which happened at more than 50 here, which
I would say is amazing, but see, now in the
midst of this rally, we will learn something from this rally, first of all we will
focus on risk management, you took entry, your stop
loss, if immediate  If it is there then this stop loss will be there, no
problem, but look at these in-between
fluctuation, look at these in-between fluctuation, look at this June fluctuation,
how dangerous the fluctuations are, but
you will not be scared, you will not be scared
because if you are riding in it, then if your
position size is controlled then you will not be scared,
but if the position size is
not controlled then you will definitely be scared, but you
see how the corrections happen in-between
and after that the stock has gone up even faster,
ICICI Lombard General Insurance has
taught a lot, it will take another stock in front of you,
Capsize Infra Project, which was
mentioned in the same video, you will
see that, but what are we learning from this,
I am presenting a larger time frame in front of you
so that you can focus and learn something from it,
if seen in a larger time frame wise,
Capsize Infra Project, you
saw ICICI Lombard General, the second
part of this video because two different stocks were
discussed at 243, this was QSite Infra,
if the price of CapSite Infra is seen then it is
a small cap category stock,
from which  Expectations are very high
but this too has not run away because everyone's
time comes and if we look at this stock,
this stock too was
consolidating here in the range of 240 creating a similar situation
and after that has it run much, I
would say that even now it has not run away much
because if you
look at it just from November till now, it has run a little bit above 70
but I would say it is a little bit
because it is a large cap category stock,
this is a small cap category stock, if it
runs towards 50 then its expectations are very
high but our expectations are not much
more than this, you
go till here in this zone and it has reached around that level, the
story beyond that will be told by the next zone,
we will expect consolidation correction here, but for now, the
expectations that will be kept in it from here,
look at this level, it is clear, you will say or this is a
very good situation, how
positivity comes and it comes back to the zone and
then you will see the rally  But
in comparison to large cap stocks, small cap stocks are expected to move very well. There is
expectation but we will look at some more
stocks, these have run away, now we will
look at those stocks and try to understand
where what opportunity is visible.
Natural Capsules, in the last few months,
pharma stocks have done wonders, that is,
pharma stocks have given such a dangerous rally
and now I will
try to show you small stocks because this
stock too, after a very fierce rally, that is,
from 25 to where it had gone, it reached the level of 500,
now it is giving a beautiful correction, is it giving or
not, but during this correction,
if you see, this stock kept falling, kept
falling, but now this stock is giving
positivity and along with it, the
hope of momentum starting here,
that is why this stock is in the radar here,
if you look at this on the daily time frame, then
you will see that the
cycle can start, see clearly,
till now it was in full bearish cycle, but
now this consolidation is there  This
takes you towards a positive cycle. This is a
natural capsule. We will look at another stock
called Indico Remedies. We will talk
about what we learn from
Indico Remedies. I will try
to present the weekly chart before you first
because what
kind of situation is this stock giving? Look at this low point, look at
this low point. You will say,
this is kind of like a low forming a base.
If you look,
you can see a slight downward trend. Here you can
see almost equal or a slight downtrend.
So this situation is a sign of a strong base.
But on the upside, this stock is
not seeing any major move right now. So, we will expect
some positivity from the consolidation here. Look at the
momentum coming back here. So, the
rejection of 200 EMA is very important for Indico Remedies in the coming week. But let's see on the daily basis.
If the cycle starts, then that will be
positive again. The cycle has not started yet. It is
just about to start next week.  It is going to be
very important for us to learn from
Indico Remedies, so we have learned from
different stocks. Today we
learned something from Capacit Infra project, we
saw divergence and all, IL&FS General
Insurance, tried to understand and learn something, then we have
Indico Remedies, then we have
Natural Capsules and two old videos
which we have, we like to learn from different
stocks and you can see from this Capacit Pharma, I will
wind up the video, please
share it, like the price section,
keep learning, practice, thank you, thank
you for watching the video